<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="#f2f2f2"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:padding="20dp"
        android:text="占位" />

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <android.support.v4.widget.NestedScrollView
            android:id="@+id/contentNSV"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:gravity="center"
                android:text="文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本文本" />

        </android.support.v4.widget.NestedScrollView>

        <!-- 必须放到一个容器中置顶位置，ScrollPullLinkage会操作marginTop来实现显示和隐藏 -->
        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/floatBarTV"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:background="#ddffffff"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:padding="10dp"
            android:text="悬浮条" />

    </FrameLayout>

</LinearLayout>